卧槽？
What the fuck?
我抓住你了！
I got you!
性交
Fuck...
哈珀
Harper.
有个警察来找你
There's a police officer here to see you.
我只是想问你一些问题
Just wants to ask you some questions.
我一小时后回来给你换绷带
I'll be back in an hour to change your bandages
你该走了
and it'll be time for you to go.
哈珀·赛克斯 我叫斯莱顿 我是一名州侦探
Harper Sykes. My name is Slayton. I'm a state detective.
我得说实话 我老板不相信你的故事
I gotta be honest. My boss doesn't believe your story.
想一想你的Wachitumi山谷之旅
Thinks your little trip through the Wachitumi Valley
是一个乡下人的童话
is a hillbilly fairy tale.
让我来这里看看你是不是另一个人
Sent me down here to find out if you're just another
一个在冰毒实验室里自焚的山地混混
mountain tweaker who burned herself up in a meth lab.
一旦你出院 她会
And once you're discharged she's gonna
把你关起来 因为你刺伤了找到你的州警察
lock you up for stabbing the state trooper who found you.
但我读了他的报告
But I read his report.
这就是我来这里的原因
And that's the reason I'm here.
我听说了Wachitumi谷
See I've been hearing about Wachitumi Valley
因为我还是个男孩
since I was a boy.
这些神话在我出生的地方很传奇
Those myths are legendary where I come from.
我以前很喜欢听
I used to love to hear about
警察杀害没有埋葬死者的天主教徒
cop-killing Catholics who didn't bury their dead,
逃跑的奴隶仍在练习巫毒
runaway slaves still practicing voodoo,
铁路上剩下的中国人自己吃
leftover Chinamen from the railroad who ate their own.
但他们只是故事哈珀
But they were just stories Harper.
这就是他们的全部 没有证据
That's all they were, no proof.
永远没有答案 没有证据
Never any answers. No evidence.
所以我来了
So I came here
从你的故事中得到一些答案
to get some answers from your story
你必须说服我你得到了
and you're going to have to convince me that you got them.
否则我们会把你关起来
Or we're going to lock you up.
报告说你身上裹着黏糊糊的纱布
Report says you were covered in a slimy gauze.
你被彻底击倒了 用刀刺伤了一名士兵的手臂
Totally whacked out, you stabbed a trooper in the arm with a knife.
你正要再次刺伤他
You were about to stab him again...
他是其中之一
He was one of them one of them.
其中之一？
One of who?
他说了很多他们来自哪里
He said plenty more where they came from.
是谁说的 哈珀？
Who said that, Harper?
是谁说的？
Who said that?
拉文纳
Ravener.
他是谁？
Who is he?
他杀了比利
He killed Billy.
比利
Billy.
比利 对 比利·哈里森 你失踪的男朋友
Billy, right, Billy Harrison, your missing boyfriend.
他们一直在打你给的电话号码
They've been ringing the phone number you gave
比利 没有回答
for Billy and no answer.
哈珀！
Harper!
- 不 比利
-No Billy.
不 比利 没有男朋友
No Billy. No boyfriend.
比利没有失踪
Billy's not missing.
拉文纳杀了他
Ravener killed him.
他的尸体在哪里？
Where's his body?
我有人在外面找尸体
I got guys out there looking for bodies.
他们还没有找到尸体 你是吗
They haven't found a body. Are you...
哈珀 你疯了吗？
Are you batshit crazy, Harper?
你就是这样吗？你他妈的疯了？
Is that what you are? You're just fucking out of your mind nuts?
操你
Fuck you.
所以你是摄影师 嗯？
So you're a photographer, huh?
拍摄野生动物的照片
Take pictures of animals in the wild.
我看了你的简历
I read your bio.
相当令人印象深刻
Pretty impressive.
拍摄了两个物种
Credited with photographing two species
被认为已经灭绝了
thought to be extinct that...
我想这意味着你的工作相当出色
I guess that means you're pretty good at your job.
哈珀 你在瓦奇图米山谷干什么？
What were you doing in the Wachitumi Valley, Harper?
正在寻找一条红蛇
Looking for a red snake.
这么特别的红蛇是什么？
What's so special amount of red snake?
我们不应该在那里
We're not supposed to be there.
你好
Hello.
嘿 我能帮你吗？
Hey, can I help you?
-  ...有什么？ - 嘿 呃
- ...with something? - Hey, uh...
是的 我需要做个报告
Yeah, I need to make a report.
可以
Okay.
我看到了什么
I saw something.
好吧
All right.
和
And?
你没事吧？
You okay?
我用相机拍照
I took pictures on my camera.
好吧
All right.
告诉你
Tell you what,
我给我们煮点咖啡
I'll make us some coffee.
你不去了解你想给我看的东西吗
And don't you go get what it is that you want to show me
然后我们就可以解决了 这是交易吗？
and then we can sort it out, is that a deal?
成交 是的
Deal, yeah.
哦 别介意他
Oh, don't mind him.
我只是偶尔雇他一次 让他远离他妈妈的头发
I just hire him every once in a while to keep him out of his mama's hair.
好吧请坐
All right. Have a seat.
嘿 哈珀 我是比利 只是打电话给你最新情况
Hey, Harper, it's Billy, just calling to give you an update.
我刚离开这座城市 我有大约五个小时的时间 直到我来到Wachitumi山谷
I just left the city, I got about five hours until I am in the Wachitumi Valley.
嗯 别给我回电话 我肯定你在树林里
And, um, don't call me back, I'm sure you're out there in the woods
拍照 超级可爱 嗯
taking photos, being super cute, um...
我要直接去床上吃早餐 我有多余的衣服给你
I'm going to head right to the bed and breakfast, I've got extra clothes for you.
嘿 嘿！
Hey, hey!
卧槽！
What the fuck!
嘿 停下！
Hey, stop!
不
No!
救命！
Somebody help!
你知道 我在去马羽毛的路上
You know, I was on my way to Horsefeathers.
我只是想看看
I was just gonna TGIF it.
你知道的？但我接到了镇上的弱智的电话
You know? But I got a call from the town retard
他说警长来过一次小小的摄影爱好者之旅
who said the sheriff had had a little shutterbug visit.
你是个小窥探者 嗯？
You're a little snoop, huh?
他说你一直在放相机
He said you've been putting your camera
你不该去的地方
where you aren't supposed to.
我是自然摄影师
I'm a nature photographer
什么
What?
- 你可以拿我的相机  - 我听不见你说话
- You can have my camera. - I can't hear you.
你可以拥有相机
You can have the camera.
我不要照相机
I don't want the camera.
你可以有照片
You can have the pictures.
我不要照片
I don't want the pictures.
我想要你
I want you.
可以
Okay?
这就是它的发展方向
Here's how it's going to go.
这将非常简单
It's going to be super simple.
你和我就要在这里决斗了 功率
You and I we're just going to duke it out right here. Pow.
这些男孩？
These boys?
他们只是来确保我做好我的工作 可以
They're just here to make sure I do my job. Okay?
所以
So...
准备好了就出来吧 亲爱的
Come on out when you're ready, sweetheart.
不要着急
No rush.
来吧 表演时间到了 女士
Come on, it's showtime, lady.
性交
Fuck.
是 啊
Yeah!
你在记分牌上
You are on the scoreboard.
这些男孩一点都不懂
These boys ain't got shit.
看看你 嗯？
Look at you, huh?
我说我会给你一个公平的机会 让你跳到我身上
I said I'd give you a fair fight, getting a jump on me.
你在哪里学的那样射击
Where'd you learn to shoot like that.
哦 是的！哦 我爱上你了
Oh, yeah! Ooh, I'm falling for you.
- 你是个疯子  - 哦 我是个疯子？
- You're a psycho. - Oh, I'm a psycho?
女孩 你刚刚自杀了
Girl, you just killed yourself somebody.
过来 你正是我一直在寻找的那种女孩
Come here, you are exactly the type of girl I have been looking for.
你真的是 你有精神！
You really are. You got spirit!
我向上帝发誓 我是说 我
I swear to God, I mean, I...
我爱上你了
I'm falling for you.
我看见你了
I saw you.
在树上把那个人撕碎
At the tree tearing that man apart.
那个人
That man...
那个人要撕裂我的山谷部分
That man was going to tear my valley part.
那个人是一名木材和矿物侦察员
That man was a timber and mineral scout.
我们用样本抓住了他
We caught him with samples.
你知道那个小混蛋要做什么吗？
You know what that little fucker was gonna do?
他去了一家大型石油公司
He goes to a big oil company,
他得到一大笔钱
he gets a big fat check,
然后他们去游说
then they go and they lobby
你知道联邦调查局介入后会发生什么吗？
and you know what happens when the feds get to it?
他们把木材和矿产权卖给出价最高的人
They sell off the timber and mineral rights to the highest bidder.
你去过西弗吉尼亚吗？
You ever been to West Virginia?
你看到他们对自己的山做了什么吗？
You see what they've done to their fucking mountains?
我所做的是保持一种生活方式
What I did was preserve a way of life.
那个混蛋会改变一切的 每件事
That fucker would have changed everything. Everything!
我看到你做了什么 噢 操！
I saw what you did. Oh, fuck!
你不明白 你这个愚蠢的婊子 我在做我相信的事 嗯？
You don't understand, you stupid bitch. I'm doing what I believe in. Hmm?
仅仅因为你相信它并不能使它正确
Just cause you believe in it doesn't make it right.
是的 是的！
Yes, it does!
你没在听！
You're not listening!
这个地方是我的！
This place is mine!
我真的以为你会感激的
And I really thought that you could appreciate this.
我们有大西洋海岸上最后一片古老的森林
We've got the last old-growth forest on the Atlantic seaboard.
就像定居者来到这里一样
It's just like when the settlers got here.
像你这样的自然女孩应该能够欣赏这一切
Nature girl like you should be able to appreciate all that.
你好
Hello?
性交！
Fuck!
不知道为什么有照片婊子在这里
Don't know why some photo bitch is up here...
可能会把她的照片寄给某个该死的探矿者
Probably sending her pictures to some fucking prospector.
成年男子
Man.
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha.
你要来这里
You gonna come here...
把我逼出山谷 我不会那样的 是的 我会找到的
Force me out of the valley. I ain't gonna have that, yeah, I'm gonna find it.
我要抓住她
I'm gonna catch her...
我要打碎她 我要打破那个婊子！
I'm gonna break her. I'm gonna break that bitch!
小贱人
Little cunt.
愚蠢的婊子
Dumb fucking bitch.
快点 婊子！
Come on, bitch!
你在哪里？
Where you at?
小红帽 从森林里回来吧？
Little Red Riding Hood, come back out of the forest, huh?
那个魔鬼在哪里？
Where's that devil?
他妈的
Fucking...
呜呜！
Woo-wee!
是 啊是 啊
Yeah. Yeah.
你听到了吗？
You hear me?
你怎么认为   ？
What do you think...?
帮助
Help.
我们怎么离开这里？
How do we get out of here?
你永远无法离开这里
You ain't ever gonna get out of here.
我接受了你 只是为了让你知道
I took you on that. Just so you know.
我有
I had...
我对你很好
I had you good.
你什么都不是
You ain't nothing.
杰西 你在吗？
Jesse, you there?
杰西？
Jesse?
哈珀·赛克斯
Harper Sykes.
我猜你会走开的 一定是你
Guess you'd be off squawking away. Had to be you.
你把钱包忘在卡车里了 所以我找了你一下
You left your wallet in the truck, so I looked you up a bit.
谷歌搜索了一下
Googled ya.
在阿肯色州寻找象牙喙啄木鸟的一个月
A month in Arkansas looking for the ivory-billed woodpecker,
然后在亚洲猎杀老虎
then hunting tigers in Asia.
你是带着相机的G.I.Jane
You're G.I. Jane with a camera.
你是真的
You're the real deal.
现在 你想知道我是否会听到你来
Now, you're wondering if I'm going to hear you coming
试着把那台钻机开走
and try to ride that rig out of there.
你在想这是否值得冒险
You're wondering whether it's worth the risk.
嗯 事情是这样的 离开山谷只有一条路
Well, here's the thing. There's only one way out of the valley.
北面的燃烧瀑布无法通行
Burning Falls to the north is impassable.
加油站向西徒步16天
The gas station is a 16-day hike to the west.
你需要将近一个月的时间
And it's going to take you nearly a month
如果你想穿过国家森林东部
if you try to go through the national forest east.
唯一的出路
The only way out of there
正在沿着河而下
is coming down the river
你知道这迟早会发生
and you know that's gonna happen sooner or later...
你好
Hello?
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
Mallinckrodt
Mallinckrodt.
哈珀·赛克斯
Harper Sykes.
赛克斯
Sykes.
非常好 好名字
Very good. Wonderful name.
想要波旁威士忌吗？是的 是的 你知道
Want a bourbon? Yes, yes, you do.
我可以用一下你的电话吗？
Could I use your phone?
我没有电话 女士
I don't have a phone, ma'am.
我已经15年没有手机了
I haven't had a phone for 15 years.
我真的需要打个电话
I just really need to make a phone call.
嗯 我们到炉火边去把你整理一下
Um, let's go in there by the fire and get you sorted.
每次我都会洒一点点
Every time I spill just a little bit.
你知道我的意思吗？
You know what I mean?
白天饮酒
Daytime drinking.
你在想
You're wondering.
这是为了我的心 所有这些东西
This is for my heart, all of this stuff.
一 二 三 这个 四
One, two, three, this, four.
这个 嗯 我的用品一周一次
This, uh, comes with my supplies once a week.
- 你的补给  - 嗯
- Your supplies. - Mm-hm.
这里的每件东西都是每周给我一次的
Everything here is delivered to me once a week.
让我留在这里
And allows me to stay here.
那些书在那里
Those books there.
它们是我们如何驯服这个山谷的文件
They're a document of how we tamed this valley.
这里到处都是被砍伐的树木
Felled trees from all around here
去河边了
Went down to the river
拿了大石头带到这里来
and got big stones and brought them up here.
那时蚊子比蜂鸟还大
And that's when there were mosquitoes bigger than hummingbirds.
还有熊到处跑来跑去杀人
And there were bears running around killing people.
这很可怕 但我们做到了
It was grim, but we did it.
我们建造了这个地方
We built this place.
我们驯服了整个山谷
We tamed this whole valley.
- 这是很多死亡  - 那里？
- It's a lot of death. - That there?
这就是文明的进步
That's the progress of civilization.
进步
Progress?
当然
Of course.
你的进步是什么意思？
What do you mean progress?
社会早已与众不同
Societies have long distinguished themselves
他们是如何自杀的
in how they killed their own.
看起来像是折磨
Seems like torture.
不 不 酷刑是完全不同的事情
No, no, torture's a whole different matter.
执行是衡量标准
Execution is the measurement
一个国家的文明
of a country's civility.
酷刑是晴雨表
Torture is the barometer
一个国家的创造力
of a nation's creativity.
你怎么杀人？你怎么让一个人活着
How do you kill people? How do you keep a man alive
足以让他说出你需要他说的话？
enough to get him to say what you need him to say?
每个人都有不同的做法
And everybody had different ways of doing it.
骄傲地说出了他们的方法
Proudly named their methods.
西班牙驴子铁娘子
The Spanish Donkey the Iron Maiden.
这是一场残酷的竞争
And there was a cruel, cruel competition
痛苦之王之间
between the Kings of Pain.
但你认为什么比什么更让人害怕？
But what do you think scares man more than anything else?
你觉得他最害怕什么？
What do you think scares him the most?
大自然之母
Mother Nature.
因为大自然是真正的痛苦之主
Because Mother Nature is the true Lord of Pain.
- 想再喝一杯吗？ - 不 谢谢
- Want another drink? - No, thanks.
如果你不介意的话 我要一个
I'm going to have one, if you don't mind.
我知道你不是自找的
I know you didn't ask for it. There you go.
你杀了它
You murder it.
哇！
Wow.
Thatta女孩
Thatta girl.
我做这件事的时候 你能过来把这件事关了吗？
While I do this can you come over here and turn this thing off?
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
你他妈的婊子
You motherfucking bitch.
赛克斯
Sykes.
赛克斯！
Sykes!
该死！
Goddamnit!
赛克斯！
Sykes!
我知道你在河边看到了什么
I know what you saw down at the river.
你拍照的地方
Where you were taking your pictures.
你看到的是一个空心十字架
What you saw was a hollow cross.
一  呃 我自己想出来的
I, uh, came up with that myself.
你继续往前跑
You run on along.
他们在等你
They're waiting for you.
…继续表示有严重雷暴
...continue to indicate a severe thunderstorm
能够产生大到高尔夫球大小的破坏性冰雹
capable of producing large damaging hail up to golf-ball size...
强烈的暴风雨
The severe storm...
……能够产生大到高尔夫球大小的破坏性冰雹
...capable of producing large, damaging hail up to golf-ball size.
这场强风暴位于普雷斯比耶附近
The severe storm is located near Presbiet...
或者在普雷斯比耶上空以每小时30英里的速度向东南移动
or about over Presbiet and moving southeast at 30 miles per hour.
警告中的其他位置包括
Further locations in the warning include
东曼杜拉西皮尔斯
East Mandura Western Pierce...
这是一个危险的情况
This is a dangerous situation.
如果你正处在这场风暴的路径上 请立即做好准备 迎接毁灭性的冰雹
If you are in the path of this storm, prepare immediately for destructive hail
这会严重损坏车顶 车窗 壁板和车辆
which can significantly damage roofs, windows, siding and vehicles.
现在在坚固的结构内寻求庇护 远离窗户
Seek shelter now inside a sturdy structure and stay away from windows.
向最近的执法机构报告任何损坏
Report any damage to the nearest law enforcement agency
用于向国家气象局转发
for relay to the National Weather Service.
你好
Hello?
嘿你好
Hey? Hello?
达琳 该死的泵又坏了 达琳？
Darlene, damn pump's out again. Darlene?
我要把左轮手枪拿出来放在地上
I'm going to take my revolver out and put it down on the ground.
比利和我从昨天起就一直在找你
Billy and I have been looking for you since yesterday.
你去过哪里？
Where you been?
你的男朋友几乎无所不包
That boyfriend of yours has covered nearly every inch
在这个山谷里寻找你
of this valley looking for you.
没关系
It's okay.
可以
Okay.
你跑到哪里去了？嗯？
Where'd you run off to? Huh?
我找到了你的卡车 我的巡洋舰里有你的东西
I found your truck. I got all your stuff in my cruiser.
好吧
Alright?
没事的
It'll be okay.
走吧
Let's go.
你能告诉我发生了什么吗？
Can you tell me what happened?
我正在逃离他们
I'm running from them.
谁
Who?
我给你看
I'll show you.
不不不
No! No! No!
在古代 斯拉夫人经常从人们那里得到答案
In ancient times the Slavs used to get answers from people
用他们的奶牛不仅仅是牛奶
by using their cows for more than just milk.
你看 消化所有的食物
You see, digesting all the food
其中一个家伙一天吃东西
that one of these guys eats in a day,
这需要一个非常特殊的系统
that requires a very special system.
这些大而漂亮的野兽有四个胃
So these big beautiful beasts they have four stomachs.
它们基本上只是一个大的旧缸
They're basically just a big old vat
世界上最有毒的酸
of the world's most toxic acid.
很久以前有这些
A long time ago there were these
- 两位奶农
-two dairy farmers.
他们推翻了这个可怕的国王
And they had overthrown this horrid king
他以最邪恶的方式而闻名
who was famous for his most wicked ways.
他只是喜欢折磨
He just loved torture.
他喜欢冲击波
He loved impalements.
他喜欢犹大摇篮
He loved Judas cradles.
他喜欢拷问棺材 所有的好东西
He loved coffin tortures. All the good stuff.
现在 这些兄弟 他们洗劫了城堡 对吧？
Now, these brothers, they'd sacked the castle, right?
国王显然对自己的困境一无所知
And the king, who obviously has no idea about his predicament,
他只是献出了他的王国
he just offers up his kingdom.
扔下女王和他的孩子 扔下村庄
Throws the queen and his children and the village
如果他们能放过他那胆小的屁股
if they'll just let his cowardly ass go.
这些革命者
These revolutionaries...
- 它们很简单
-they're just simple
小奶农
little dairy farmers.
对他们来说 你知道 这听起来不对
And to them, you know, this doesn't sound right.
所以…他们在国王的宫廷里举办了一场盛大的宴会
So... they throw a huge banquet in the king's court.
每个人都在那里 整个王室
Everybody's there, the whole royal family.
兄弟们坐在那里 他们都在玩得很开心
The brothers are sitting there and they're all just having a grand time.
然后有人牵着一头牛进来
Then somebody leads a cow in.
其中一个兄弟 他站了起来
One of the brothers, he gets up.
他走向宴会桌
He goes to the banquet table
他拿出一把巨大的雕刻刀
and he takes out a huge carving knife.
然后奶农拿起一把刀
Then the dairy farmer takes a knife.
他在肛门下面造了一个小洞
He creates a small cavity just below the anus.
然后另一个兄弟 他绑着国王的脚
Then the other brother, he binds the king's feet.
还有他的手
And his hands.
然后让所有人震惊的是
And then to everyone's shock,
他们把国王滑进牛体内
they slide the king inside the cow.
他们开始缝合国王的脖子
They start stitching up around the king's neck.
这些斯拉夫人都见过
These Slavs had seen it all.
他们的国王
Their king...
头伸出小腿
with a head sticking out of a calf.
这是新的 这是开创性的
This was new this was groundbreaking.
他们说 国王的尸体大约需要三天才能分解
They said it took about three days for the king's body to decompose.
你在笑什么？
What are you laughing at?
我在老人家看到了你们所有人的照片
I saw the picture of all of you at the old man's house.
这就是你笑的地方？
That's what you're laughing at?
我杀了他们所有人
I killed all of them.
是 啊我把金赛那家伙的脸炸了
Yeah. I blew that Kinsey guy's face off.
还有调整器
And the tweaker...
他被枪杀了
He got shot to pieces.
然后是那个面带微笑的令人毛骨悚然的家伙
And then that creepy guy with the smile.
失去了理智
Lost his head.
还有那个老病发的疯子
And that old sick demented fuck.
他自己患上了冰毒诱发的心脏病
He had himself a meth-induced heart attack.
他非常痛苦
He was in a lot of pain.
所以我杀了他
So I shot him.
是的 我得到了你整个该死的家族
Yeah, I got your whole fucked-up clan.
嗯 还有更多的来源
Well, there's a lot more where that came from.
你是找不到我的懦夫
You're the coward who couldn't find me.
你让一个疲惫的警察来接我吗？
You get some tired cop to come pick me up?
解开我
Untie me.
这样我就能把你他妈的脸抓下来
So I can claw your fucking face off.
是 啊
Yeah.
我要折磨你
I'm going to torture you.
- 你是吗？ - 是 啊
- You are? - Yeah.
然后我要杀了你
And then I'm gonna kill you.
是 啊
Yeah.
然后
Then...
我要把你拖过去
I'm going to drag you across...
地板到那扇门
the floor over to that door.
我要去看猪
I'm going to watch the pigs
- 把你撕碎
-tear you apart.
- 来吧 - 你这个混蛋！
- Come on. - You motherfucker!
我抓住你了 你这个混蛋！
I got you, you motherfucker!
我抓住你了 你这个混蛋
I got you, you motherfucker.
不
No?
哈珀！
Harper!
医生拿着化验结果等着你
The doctor is waiting for you with the lab results.
你该走了
And it's time for you to go.
等待
Wait.
我快完了
I'm almost done.
他打了我之后
After he beat me...
没人在乎
And no one cares...
在他刺伤我之后
After he stabbed me.
在他把我男朋友喂给他的猪之后
After he fed my boyfriend to his pig.
不
No!
在他把我倒挂之后
After he hung me upside down
把我丢了
and left me for dead.
在他恐吓我之后
After he terrorized me.
他宰了一头牛之后
After he butchered a cow.
并将其掏空
And gutted it.
缝合后
After stitching...
你要去哪里 金杰？
Where are you going, Ginger?
你会错过最好的部分
You're gonna miss the best part.
我想你病了
I think you're ill.
我认为你是危险的阿片类药物流行的受害者
I think you are the victim of a dangerous opioid epidemic and...
你有麻烦了 你和你在一起的人
you're troubled, and you and whoever you're hanging out with...
对你自己构成极大的危险
pose a great danger to yourselves.
斯莱顿警探 请把门关上
Detective Slayton, shut the door, please.
在你警官的报告中说我的病人被覆盖了
In your officer's report it says my patient was covered
在凡士林状的物质中 她的烧伤
in a Vaseline-like substance and that her burns
- 可能是爆炸的结果  - 我知道这一切
- are the likely result of an explosion. - I know all that.
她身上没有凡士林
She wasn't covered in Vaseline.
并不是热量造成了她的三度烧伤
And it wasn't heat which created her third degree burns.
他们是什么样的烧伤？
What kind of burns are they?
实验室报告说她进行了防腐处理
The lab report states that she was embalmed
在牛胆汁的消化酶中
in the digestive enzymes of ox bile.
她正在被消化
She was being digested.